<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Transfer Market</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed_player">TabbedPlayerActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Image</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Info</string>
    <string name="welcome_header">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="the_application_logo">The Application Logo</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="enter_your_e_mail">Enter your e-mail</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="confirm_your_password">Confirm your password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="value">Value</string>
    <string name="position">Position</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="club">Club</string>
    <string name="nation">Nation</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="lewa_name">Robert Lewandowski</string>
    <string name="lewa_value">€45.00m</string>
    <string name="poland">Poland</string>
    <string name="barca">FC Barcelona</string>
    <string name="lewa_age">Age:34</string>
    <string name="lewa_info">Robert Lewandowski is a Polish professional footballer who plays as a striker for La Liga club Barcelona and captains the Poland national team. Recognized for his positioning, technique and finishing, Lewandowski is considered one of the best strikers of all time, as well as one of the most successful players in Bundesliga history. He has scored over 600 senior career goals for club and country.\n\n
        After being the top scorer in the third and second tiers of Polish football with Znicz Pruszków, Lewandowski moved to top-flight Lech Poznań, helping the team win the 2009–10 Ekstraklasa. In 2010, he transferred to Borussia Dortmund, where he won honors including two consecutive Bundesliga titles and the league\'s top goalscorer award. In 2013, he also featured with Dortmund in the 2013 UEFA Champions League Final. Prior to the start of the 2014–15 season, Lewandowski agreed to join Dortmund\'s domestic rivals, Bayern Munich, on a free transfer. In Munich, he won the Bundesliga title in every one of his eight seasons. Lewandowski was integral in Bayern\'s UEFA Champions League win in 2019–20 as part of a treble. He is one of only two players, alongside Johan Cruyff, to achieve the European treble while being the highest goalscorer in all three competitions, and the first to do it as the sole top scorer.
        \n\n In 2020, Lewandowski won the Best FIFA Men"'"s Player Award (retained in 2021) and the UEFA Men"'"s Player of the Year Award. On 19 July 2022, Lewandowski signed for La Liga club Barcelona on a four-year contract for a fee of €45 million, potentially rising to €50 million with add-ons.</string>
    <string name="salah_name">Mohamed Salah</string>
    <string name="salah_value">€90.00m</string>
    <string name="rw">Right Winger</string>
    <string name="egypt">Egypt</string>
    <string name="salah_info">\"Mohamed Salah Hamed Mahrous Ghaly\"(born 15 June 1992) is an Egyptian professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Liverpool and captains the Egypt national team. Considered one of the best players in the world, he is known for his finishing, dribbling, and speed.
     \n\nSalah started his senior career in 2010 playing for Al Mokawloon, departing in 2012 to join Basel, where he won two Swiss Super League titles. In 2014, Salah joined Chelsea for a reported fee of £11 million, but limited gametime led to successive loans to Fiorentina and Roma, who later signed him permanently for €15 million. In 2017, Salah was the subject of a then-club record association football transfer when he signed for Liverpool for £36.9 million, becoming the most expensive Egyptian player of all time.\n\n
        Salah went on to be an integral player in the club"'"s Champions League and Premier League title successes the following two seasons, and has since also won the Community Shield, the FA Cup and the League Cup. Salah has achieved numerous individual accolades, including two PFA Players"'" Player of the Year awards, three Premier League Golden Boots, the Premier League Player of the Season, the Premier League Playmaker of the Season, and finished third for the Best FIFA Men"'"s Player in 2018 and 2021. He received the 2018 FIFA Puskás Award for his winning strike in the first Merseyside derby of the 2017–18 season. "\</string>
    <string name="liverpool">Liverpool</string>
    <string name="salah_age">Age:30</string>
    <string name="messi_info">Lionel Andrés Messi, also known as Leo Messi, is an Argentine professional footballer who plays as a forward for Ligue 1 club Paris Saint-Germain and captains the Argentina national team. Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time. Messi has won a record seven Ballon d\'Or awards,a record six European Golden Shoes, and in 2020 was named to the Ballon d\'Or Dream Team.\n\nUntil leaving the club in 2021, he had spent his entire professional career with Barcelona, where he won a club-record 35 trophies
    , including ten La Liga titles, seven Copa del Rey titles and four UEFA Champions Leagues. A prolific goalscorer and creative playmaker, Messi holds the records for most goals in La Liga (474), a La Liga and European league season (50), most hat-tricks in La Liga (36) and the UEFA Champions League (8), and most assists in La Liga (192), a La Liga season (21) and the Copa América (17). He also holds the record for most international goals by a South American male (90). Messi has scored over 780 senior career goals for club and country, and has the most goals by a player for a single club. </string>
    <string name="messi_name">Lionel Messi</string>
    <string name="messi_value">€50.00m</string>
    <string name="argentina">Argentina</string>
    <string name="psg">PSG</string>
    <string name="messi_age">Age:35</string>
    <string name="cf">Centre-Forward</string>
    <string name="ronaldo_value">€20.00m</string>
    <string name="cr7_name">Cristiano Ronaldo</string>
    <string name="portugal">Portugal</string>
    <string name="man_united">Man United</string>
    <string name="cr7_age">Age:37</string>
    <string name="cr7_info">\"Cristiano Ronaldo dos Santos Aveiro (born 5 February 1985) is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Manchester United and captains the Portugal national team. Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time, Ronaldo has won five Ballon d\'Or awards and four European Golden Shoes, the most by a European player. He has won 32 trophies in his career, including seven league titles, five UEFA Champions Leagues, one UEFA European Championship and one UEFA Nations League. Ronaldo holds the records for most appearances (181), most goals (140) and assists (42) in the Champions League, most goals in the European Championship (14), most international goals by a male player (115), and most international appearances by a European male (184). He is one of the few players to have made over 1,100 professional career appearances, and has scored over 800 official senior career goals for club and country. \n\n
        Ronaldo began his senior career with Sporting CP, before signing with Manchester United in 2003, aged 18, winning the FA Cup in his first season. He would also go on to win three consecutive Premier League titles, the Champions League and the FIFA Club World Cup; at age 23, he won his first Ballon d\'Or. Ronaldo was the subject of the then-most expensive association football transfer when he signed for Real Madrid in 2009 in a transfer worth €94 million (£80 million), where he won 15 trophies, including two La Liga titles, two Copa del Rey, and four Champions Leagues, and became the club\'s all-time top goalscorer. He won back-to-back Ballons d\'Or in 2013 and 2014, and again in 2016 and 2017, and was runner-up three times behind Lionel Messi, his perceived career rival. In 2018, he signed for Juventus in a transfer worth an initial €100 million (£88 million), the most expensive transfer for an Italian club and for a player over 30 years old. He won two Serie A titles, two Supercoppe Italiana, and a Coppa Italia, before returning to Manchester United in 2021.\n\n
        Ronaldo made his international debut for Portugal in 2003 at the age of 18 and has since earned over 190 caps, making him Portugal\'s most-capped player. With more than 100 goals at international level, he is also the nation\'s all-time top goalscorer. Ronaldo has played in and scored at 11 major tournaments; he scored his first international goal at Euro 2004, where he helped Portugal reach the final. He assumed captaincy of the national team in July 2008. In 2015, Ronaldo was named the best Portuguese player of all time by the Portuguese Football Federation. The following year, he led Portugal to their first major tournament title at Euro 2016, and received the Silver Boot as the second-highest goalscorer of the tournament. He also led them to victory in the inaugural UEFA Nations League in 2019, and later received the Golden Boot as top scorer of Euro 2020. \"</string>
    <string name="rma">Real Madrid</string>
    <string name="france">France</string>
    <string name="benz_value">€30.00m</string>
    <string name="benz_name">Karim Benzema</string>
    <string name="benz_info">Karim Mostafa Benzema is a French professional footballer who plays as a striker for Spanish club Real Madrid and the France national team. A creative forward known for his playmaking and finishing, Benzema is regarded as one of the best strikers in the world. He ranks as Real Madrid\'s all-time second-highest goalscorer and all-time top assist provider.\n\n
    Born in Lyon to Algerian parents, Benzema began his senior career with hometown club Olympique Lyonnais in 2005, contributing sporadically to three Ligue 1 title wins. In 2008, he was named the league\'s Player of the Year and in the Team of the Year having finished as the league\'s top goalscorer and winning his fourth league title and first Coupe de France. In 2009, Benzema was the subject of a then French record football transfer when signed for Real Madrid in a transfer worth €35 million. After struggling to establish himself in his debut season, he eventually achieved a consistent goalscoring rate with the club, and notably went on to be part of a highly rated trio alongside Cristiano Ronaldo and Gareth Bale — dubbed BBC — who were integral to a period
        where Real Madrid won four UEFA Champions League titles from 2014 to 2018.\n\n
    Following Ronaldo\'s departure in 2018, Benzema transitioned from the false 9 position into a sole striker. His prominence in Real Madrid\'s squad significantly increased, with him being named in the La Liga Team of the Season in 2018–19, 2019–20, 2020–21 and 2021–22, awarded the league\'s Best Player in 2019–20 and 2021–22, and also winning the Pichichi Trophy in 2021–22.
    Captaining the team, his notable career-high performances during Real Madrid\'s victory in the 2021–22 Champions League have been hailed as one of the finest individual campaigns in the competition\'s history, in addition to becoming the top scorer and winning the Player of the Season award. Benzema has won 23 trophies with Real Madrid, including four La Liga, two Copa del Rey, and five Champions League titles. </string>
    <string name="kdb_age">Age:31</string>
    <string name="man_city">Man City</string>
    <string name="belgium">Belgium</string>
    <string name="kdb_info">\"Kevin De Bruyne (born 28 June 1991) is a Belgian professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Premier League club Manchester City and the Belgium national team. De Bruyne is widely regarded as one of the best players in the world, and has often been described as a \"complete footballer\".\n\n De Bruyne began his career at Genk, where he was a regular player when they won the 2010–11 Belgian Pro League. In 2012, he joined English club Chelsea, where he was used sparingly and then loaned to Werder Bremen. He signed with Wolfsburg for £18 million in 2014, where he established himself as one of the best players in the Bundesliga and was integral in the club\'s 2014–15 DFB-Pokal win. In the summer of 2015, De Bruyne joined Manchester City for a club record £54 million. He has since won three Premier League titles, five League Cups and an FA Cup with the club. In 2017–18, he had a significant role in Manchester City\'s record in becoming the only Premier League team to attain 100 points in a single season. In 2019–20, De Bruyne tied the record for most assists in a Premier League season and was awarded Player of the Season. \"</string>
    <string name="am">Attacking Midfield</string>
    <string name="kdb_value">€85.00m</string>
    <string name="kdb_name">Kevin De Bruyne</string>
    <string name="haaland_age">Age:22</string>
    <string name="norway">Norway</string>
    <string name="haaland_value">€150.00m</string>
    <string name="haaland_name">Erling Haaland</string>
    <string name="lw">Left Winger</string>
    <string name="spurs">Spurs</string>
    <string name="south_korea">South Korea</string>
    <string name="son_value">€75.00m</string>
    <string name="son_name">Heung-min Son</string>
    <string name="chelsea">Chelsea</string>
    <string name="dm">Defensive Midfield</string>
    <string name="kante_value">€40.00m</string>
    <string name="kante_name">N\'Golo Kanté</string>
    <string name="kante_info">\"N\'Golo Kanté (born 29 March 1991) is a French professional footballer who plays as a central midfielder for Premier League club Chelsea and the France national team. Considered by many to be one of the world\'s best midfielders, Kanté is widely praised for his work rate and defensive acumen. Kanté made his senior professional debut with Boulogne in 2012, appearing as a substitute in one Ligue 2 match, and played an entire season in the third division the following year. After that he joined Ligue 2 side Caen on a free transfer, finished third and won promotion to Ligue 1. He stayed with the club for one more year.\n\n In 2015, Kanté joined Leicester City for a fee worth £5.6 million and was integral to their maiden Premier League victory. The following year, he joined Chelsea for a fee worth £32 million and again won the league, making him the first outfield player to win consecutive English league titles with different clubs since Eric Cantona in 1992 and 1993. He has also won the PFA Players\' Player of the Year and FWA Footballer of the Year, an FA Cup, the UEFA Europa League, and the UEFA Champions League. He was named the UEFA Men\'s Midfielder of the year in 2021. \"</string>
    <string name="dona_age">Age:23</string>
    <string name="italy">Italy</string>
    <string name="gk">Goalkeeper</string>
    <string name="dona_name">Gianluigi Donnarumma</string>
    <string name="dona_info">Gianluigi Donnarumma (born 25 February 1999) is an Italian professional footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for Ligue 1 club Paris Saint-Germain and the Italy national team.\n\n Coming through the team\'s youth system, Donnarumma began his career with AC Milan in 2015, becoming the second-youngest goalkeeper ever to debut in Serie A, aged 16 years and 242 days; he immediately broke into the starting line-up, earning a reputation as arguably the most promising young goalkeeper in the world at the time. In 2021, Donnarumma helped Milan secure a second place finish in the 2020–21 Serie A and qualification for the 2021–22 UEFA Champions League after an eight-year absence. He was also named Serie A\'s Best Goalkeeper of the Year, IFFHS World\'s Best Goalkeeper and also won the Yashin Trophy. After six years with Milan, Donnarumma moved to Ligue 1 side Paris Saint-Germain in June 2021 on a free transfer.\n \n Internationally, Donnarumma broke the record as the youngest Italy under-21 player ever to play, aged 17 years and 28 days in March 2016. Six months later, he made his senior international debut, becoming the youngest goalkeeper ever to appear for Italy, aged 17 years and 189 days. Donnarumma represented Italy at UEFA Euro 2020, helping the team win the tournament and winning the Player of the Tournament award.</string>
    <string name="vini_name">Vinicius Junior</string>
    <string name="vini_value">€120.00m</string>
    <string name="brazil">Brazil</string>
    <string name="kim_name">Joshua Kimmich</string>
    <string name="kim_value">€80.00m</string>
    <string name="kim_age">Age:27</string>
    <string name="bayern">Bayern Munich</string>
    <string name="germany">Germany</string>
    <string name="martin_name">Gabriel Martinelli</string>
    <string name="arsenal">Arsenal</string>
    <string name="martin_age">Age:21</string>
    <string name="vini_info">Vinícius José Paixão de Oliveira Júnior (born 12 July 2000), commonly known as Vinícius Júnior or Vini Jr.  is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a winger for La Liga club Real Madrid and the Brazil national team. Considered as one of the best players in the world, he is known for his dribbling skills, high pace and shooting.\n\nBorn in São Gonçalo, Vinícius began his professional career at Flamengo, where he made his senior debut in 2017, at age 16. A few weeks later, Vinícius was the subject of a transfer to La Liga club Real Madrid, for whom he signed for in a £38 million deal, which was a national record for an U-18 player. The transfer was made effective after his 18th birthday, with Vinícius debuting for the club in 2018–19. By his fourth season, Vinícius established himself as a prominent member in Real Madrid\'s squad, helping the club win the 2021–22 La Liga title and scoring the winning goal in Real Madrid\'s 2022 UEFA Champions League Final win.</string>
    <string name="martin_info">\"Gabriel Teodoro Martinelli Silva (born 18 June 2001), known as Gabriel Martinelli, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Arsenal and the Brazil national team.\n\n Born and raised in Guarulhos, Martinelli began his senior club career playing for Ituano, prior to signing for Arsenal in July 2019, aged 18.\n\nAt international level, Martinelli represents the Brazil under-23s. He helped Brazil win an Olympic Gold in men\'s football at the 2020 Summer Olympics. \"</string>
    <string name="kim_info">Joshua Walter Kimmich (born 8 February 1995) is a German professional footballer who plays as a defensive midfielder or right-back for Bundesliga club Bayern Munich and the Germany national team. He is known for his complete playstyle, versatility, aggression, and playmaking ability. He is often compared with former Bayern Munich captain Philipp Lahm and is considered his successor.\n\nAfter coming through RB Leipzig\'s youth academy, Kimmich began playing for the club\' first team in 2013. Two years later, he joined Bayern Munich. In the 2019–20 season, after winning the continental treble with Bayern Munich, Kimmich was included in the UEFA Team of the Year, the FIFA FIFPro Men\'s World11, and was recognized as the UEFA Champions League Defender of the Season.</string>
    <string name="son_info">Son Heung-min is (born 8 July 1992) is a South Korean professional footballer who plays as a forward for the Premier League club Tottenham Hotspur and captains the South Korea national team. Widely regarded as one of the best wingers in the world, as well as one of the best Asian footballers in history, Son was the first Asian player to score more than 50 goals in the Premier League, and was nominated for the Ballon d\'Or in 2019. He is known for his explosive speed, finishing, two-footedness and ability to link play.\n\nBorn in Chuncheon, Gangwon Province, Son relocated to Germany to join Hamburger SV at 16, making his debut in the Bundesliga in 2010. In 2013, he moved to Bayer Leverkusen for a club record €10 million before signing for Tottenham for £22 million two years later, becoming the most expensive Asian player in history. While at Tottenham, Son became the top Asian goalscorer in both Premier League and Champions League history, and surpassed Cha Bum-kun\'s record for most goals scored by a Korean player in European competition.  In 2019, he became the second Asian in history to reach and start a UEFA Champions League final after compatriot Park Ji-sung. In the 2021–22 season, he won, shared alongside Mohamed Salah, the Premier League Golden Boot award with 23 goals, becoming the first Asian player to win it.\n\nA full international since 2010, Son has represented South Korea at the 2014 and 2018 FIFA World Cups and is his country\'s joint top scorer at World Cups, tied with Park Ji-sung and Ahn Jung-hwan on three goals. Son has also represented South Korea at the 2018 Asian Games, where the team won gold, and the 2011, 2015, and 2019 editions of the AFC Asian Cup. Korea was the runner-up in 2015. Outside of football, Son is viewed as a symbol of national pride in South Korea for his achievements, and has been listed in Forbes Korea Power Celebrity 40 since 2019, where he ranked third in 2022. In June 2022, Son received the Cheongnyong Medal, the highest order of merit for achievement in sports given to a South Korea citizen, for his achievements in football. He is credited with causing a large uptick in interest in and the number of supporters of Tottenham among South Koreans and even East Asians more broadly, resulting in the club\'s social media strategy altering in order to target and cater to Koreans using both the club\'s standard English language accounts and their newer accounts in Korean.</string>
    <string name="haaland_info">\"Erling Braut Haaland is a Norwegian professional footballer who plays as a striker for Premier League club Manchester City and the Norway national team. Considered one of the best players in the world, he is known for his athleticism, speed and finishing. \n\nComing through the youth system, Haaland played at senior level for Bryne\'s reserve and senior teams. He moved to Molde in 2017 (also playing for their reserve team), with whom he spent two seasons. Haaland signed with Austrian Bundesliga side Red Bull Salzburg in January 2019, winning two league titles and one Austrian Cup. In December 2019, he moved to German Bundesliga club Borussia Dortmund, where he won the DFB-Pokal in 2020–21. Haaland won several individual awards and broke various records during his career. During the 2019–20 season with Salzburg, he became the first teenager to score in five consecutive UEFA Champions League matches. He was top scorer of the Champions League the following season. In 2020, Haaland won the Golden Boy award, while in 2021 he was named Bundesliga Player of the Season and was included in the FIFA FIFPro World11 in 2021. Haaland has represented Norway at various youth levels. In the 2019 FIFA U-20 World Cup, he won the tournament\'s Golden Boot, after scoring a record nine goals in a single match. He made his senior international debut in September 2019. \"</string>
</resources>